Nadai Hakone Soba
Well, but ekisoba is usually up there.
I'm often at Ebisu's ekisoba.
By the way, what do you order when you go to ekisoba?
Meat soba
Meat soba.
Or kamajire soba.
Meat soba is also good.
I'm sure it's very rich.
Time? It's already turning.
Oh...
Good evening. I was making a lot of small talk.
No, no, no, no...
What's the best ekisoba? We were all talking about that.
We were talking about ekisoba.
I'm sure you love ekisoba too.
I hear you use it a lot.
I'm sure you're familiar with it.
I'm sure you know a lot about it.
If you send it to me, there's a great line for standing-only noodle shops... especially at lunch time.
Especially during lunch time, you can go there if it's before 12:00, but as soon as 12:05 hits, you're out of there.
Well... may I begin?
What's up, Princess Yona?
Hello, Princess Yona.
I was wondering what role I'd play.
I'm that lowly guy...
He's like... You know, that guy...
You were the first one.
I had just been shown Hoshina's musical.
Master came to see it.
I ended up with the same hair color as Yona.
Just so.
That's why I usually listen to live music by an artiste, but I don't have any connections with him, so I don't see plays or musicals like that.
I don't see many plays or musicals, so I like them.
And there were a lot of people there, so I was in a lot of places.
What I wanted to say was that she sang a lot.
I mean, she sang so hard, but in the end she was beaten up by a boss character...
About half of the material in "Kannai Devil" this week was by Mr. Yanase.
If you went to see the show, you probably know who he is, but he's that musical singer who sings so well.
He used to be a member of Gekidan Shiki.
He's a member of the Shiki Theater Company.
The Shiki Theatre Company's production of "Don't Worry, Don't Worry" was...
Well, well, well... the Lion King. - The Lion King.
That's the Lion King.
So, musicals and plays like that are very new to me.
I'm sure it's a lot of rehearsal work, but...
It's been so long since I've been in a theater.
I've been in rehearsal all the time.
I was in rehearsal.
I was practicing and touring, so it was progressing without me knowing it.
We were doing live shows every day, and things were going on before I knew it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So you were very busy.
That's the only time I felt like a celebrity.
Good evening.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, sir.
How's it feel?
What's it like?
Yeah, recently.
Recently?
Recently, you know, with the "Let's build muscles" campaign?
Yes, I'm in love with it.
But it's thin, really thin.
Yes, it's thin.
Still thin.
Thin to the level of a computer
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Where is it now?
Are you a MacBook Air?
Yes, I'm still an Air
I'm still an Air, and I'm thinking about getting to the level of an iMac.
But you see, muscles are often talked about.
Muscles for show, real muscles, and inner muscles.
Inner muscles
It's a little different, isn't it?
I want to build muscles for show.
I want to build muscles that show.
I want to have muscles that are easy to see, right?
I'm surprised to see your shoulders suddenly bouncing around in the "SAWAPON" section.
Every time when she does her sns, her face looks like this.
He's so tanned. That's cool and all, but you're right.
I'm a little different. I'm the type of guy who has trouble building muscle on the outside.
I'm the type of guy who doesn't have muscles on the outside... even when I was a skinny soccer player... but when you touch it... it looks so soft... you can't see it...
The key to changing that is the calf muscles on my legs and back and feet.
I saw a compilation of pictures from Idolfest the other day, and I really liked all the poses she did, like this one, with her feet right here.
I mean, I want to have a good look at them, but I don't want them to look like that.
I don't want it to look like that, but I want it to look like a foot that's really up in the image.
I'd like to see something like that. Please take a picture and fix my feet.
I'm usually like this... but I remembered that music from the jump...
I remember that music article in Natalie's music magazine...
I remember there was an article in the Natalie magazine that said that EbiChu was going to change into a new organization and there was a picture of them.
And then all the girls were gathered together on stage and they were yelling "yay"...
I wanted to have a picture of one of them jumping up and down like this.
He's jumping like this!
He can jump so well!
There's a song by Ebichu called "Haitateki" where they jump at the end of the chorus.
I was in charge of the jump, and the person who always took the pictures of Atari-san timed his exclusive jump perfectly.
I was in charge of the jump at the end of the chorus, and the person who always takes the pictures of Mr. Atari was perfect in timing the exclusive jumps.
I think he is the best jump photographer in the world, even if his jumping ability is so great that even the person who is taking the picture is concerned about it.
He never misses the right moment, he's so cool!
I mean, it was a long time ago...
I'm going to continue to look for it.
I'm going to go with you because of the boom in the suit...
I'll tell you what's in the letter... a meteor shower... ah... ah...
I saw a meteor shower...
I saw it today, and I thought it was just now, so I went out to see it, but I don't know how it started.
I don't know how it opens.
I don't think you can see it when it's bright.
It's relatively dark at around 3:00 a.m.
So I was looking at it for about an hour, wondering how I could have noticed it at such a perfect time.
I was looking at it for about an hour, but I couldn't see it, and when you look at a picture like that, you start to see an illusion.
I felt like I was seeing a hugh, and I'm sure it was.
By the way, there was a person who sent me that letter.
Mr. Makumaku, Yokohama City
There's no "DeVille in the museum, space is bad" corner, but...
Good evening, I'm Devil Makumaku, and this is the Perseid meteor shower.
I saw a shooting star. I left my iPhone's video camera running, so I was able to take a movie of it.
I left my iPhone's video camera running, so I was able to take a movie of it.
So, are you sure? Are you sure?
You can do that with an iPhone?
Send me some. It's a wonderful time, isn't it?
Yukiri-chan, this master... this master...
The air in the MacBook looked like stars.
Indeed. I can already see them.
I'm reading it now. It's spinning. Is this the universe?
Is this the solar system? Solar system, galaxy...
It's spinning. Let's load it one more time.
Let's try again. - Hang in there, Wi-Fi.
Come on, I think we're getting a little Wi-Fi in here.
Wi-Fi doesn't say Wi-Fi.
Is there any Wi-Fi here?
But something's going on, but it's got antennas all over the place.
Wait a minute, it's not loading.
I have to open something or press something or something...
Oh, no! It's gone round and round and round. It's probably faster to download it here.
How long is it? I think it's too short.
Can you do it? Then this should be good.
Save it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let's leave this galaxy here for a minute. Is this okay? Is this okay?
Where is it? Where is it?
Let's do it again. Push the green one a little bit.
Okay? Press it. Top left or something.
Ah! Aah! Aah!
What? Here, it went up, right?
Really? Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here. What?
Here. Here. Why? Here.
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here!
Oh, my God! That's great! They're here.
Wow! Impressive! Wow!
Here, here, here, here.
Here, here, here, here. What?
I didn't know you could take such beautiful pictures.
Amazing iPhone.
If you decide to do this, you're looking at garbage, right?
No, this one, this one, this one, I think they're all UFOs.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's for sure.
They disappear so quickly.
I think that's what makes them UFOs.
Hmm...
Oh, wow.
That's great.
It's going up.
Yeah, it is.
I was expecting it to be like a pew.
That's right. Gravity has nothing to do with it.
That's right.
I see... I see...
Maybe I could have seen it, too.
I didn't find it.
I was picturing something like this, so I was like...
It was the other way.
Hey, Hugh.
I wonder if he's saying that...
I'll make a wish to see a little bit of maintenance
The stars are really nice
I'm in
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
And... and... and... and... and... and...
And...
I'll tell you what I want.
I'm in for harassment.
Gross harassment?
Gross harassment.
What?
No, no, no.
I don't know what kind of harassment.
It changes the meaning a little bit.
It's just a feeling.
It's a mild form of gun harassment.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mild.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay?
May I?
Oh, my God.
Recently...
We've been making Gundam plastic models of Gundam.
And show it off to each other and grin.
There are couples who make Gundam models and show them off to each other.
Mr. Gajitani (Osaka City, Osaka Prefecture)
Master Bite-chan's regular customer, Mr. Ponkotsu!
Good evening, I'm Devil.
Oh!
The other day, I saw Master harassing Maya Mayama, short for "Gundam Harassment".
I'm sure this is from the Mayama Mayama show.
He was saying that Master came over, but all he really talked about was Gundam.
Wait a minute, that's funny, because he asked me to talk about Gundam.
That's crazy.
He only talks about Gundam.
By the way, this guy... who used to make Gundam models as a boy... has stayed away from Gundam for a long time.
But this time, after a long time, he decided to try his hand at Gunpla.
I decided to give Gunpla a try for the first time in a long time.
I decided to try my hand at making a Gundam model kit based on the image of the EBECHU girls.
I made the Gundam Aerial from the Mobile Suit Gundam Comet Witch in the purple color of the Maya Mayama!
Paint it.
I named it Gundam Maya Real.
Painted it.
I had so much fun that I thought I'd make one in the image of the other member sarpon masters!
First of all, it looks like this
Wow!
Cute! I didn't know it was this size!
Yes, there's an SD Gundam that's a little deformed and tiny.
Look at this one! So cute!
I'm sure you'll get mad at me, but...
It looks a little like Frieza.
It's a little like Frieza's coloring.
That's for sure!
If I cross them, I'll be harassed by the Ganharas.
Don't worry about it.
Yes, yes, yes.
And now, Mr. Rosso...
Katsushika-ku, Tokyo
Thank you very much.
To the Devil Gunpla Department in the museum
Master Sarpon's
Sarpon
Bite shrimp chew
Chankonban Devil, you're pieced together and cut off at the weirdest places.
Master Sarpon Bite's Ebichu Chankomban Devil
Make a Sakurai Emma appearance with the gunpla you have on hand
Master
Is it written?
Yes, it's written.
This is crazy.
Even if she didn't write it.
If you didn't write it, you're relying on me too much.
It's written, so it's OK.
It's the same as "Yah".
You can't make him depend on you.
If he didn't write anything, he shouldn't have done it.
That's why I said, "Yah!
I bought an airbrush for this
but it was quite difficult.
I'm not satisfied with the result.
I'll send you a picture.
Thank you very much!
He said he wanted Gambanari to take a look at it.
Well, today, Gamban Nari was...
ABC is coming in any minute now.
Oh my God!
What do you think of the Japanese?
Great, but what does that have to do with what you just said?
Good, good, good.
So, what do you think of Sakurai Keima's appearance in the film?
May I? Yes.
You're so good! Amazing!
If I said you weren't good, I'd say you were bad.
It's so cool!
Expectations are also in orange.
That's awesome!
This is so cool!
Is this Justice?
Yeah, it is.
It's so cool.
This is totally
It's a good level to be released.
I don't have any fans of mine with beans like this.
No, no, no, no...
I want it... but it's a Gundam... I'm not very good at this...
I've been told I'm hungry, guys! I think I'm gonna be here a lot today!
I'll be told I'm clumsy and helpless.
Let's go, guys, right now.
I'm more like... Hoshina Mirei's exclusive Zaku...
I like it... Zaku is a fighting model that opposes the Gundam...
It's very popular. Like Char's Zaku.
I've heard of Char.
Something like that.
So cool!
It's like this...
I love the Gunpla club!
It's great. It's great that it's spread so widely.
Gunpla was originally very popular all over Japan.
You just pretended to ignore it until now.
You're talking like you're on a roll here, but it's already very popular.
It's amazing, originally.
In so many ways.
Let's take a look at this corner, shall we?
I've got a fan!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Hurry up and be cool!
I'm so excited to write!
Where... where... where...
He's gone!
Oh, yes!
What's wrong?
Let's go.
I'm having fun!
No, again... you're acting like a nice guy.
You're trying to be a nice guy.
I don't know...
I can't help who I am.
I'm at an age where I'm...
You're trying to be popular.
I was trying to be cool... at my age.
It's true, this week was all about being popular, wasn't it?
By the way, they sent us a gazelle from the badlands of Hyogo Prefecture.
May I have the creature's name?
Gazelle.
Isn't it strong?
Gazer.
Gazer?
Gaither!
GIZER Gundam.
Geezer Gundam, indeed.
There it is! Yes!
Gaiser Gundam
Thank you very much!
Gaither.
Gaither?
Who?
I mean, who? I mean, that's the name of the creature.
It's not a who.
That's what you're supposed to imagine.
What kind? What kind?
Like, fishy.
What do you mean, "fishy"?
Spill it again, hint.
Animal or something.
Gaither.
I'll give you one hint.
It's not the official name of that society or these places.
It's a dialect.
Beetles and stag beetles, for example...
For example, stag beetles and stag beetles are called "stag beetles" and "kabuto" all over Japan.
But in some regions, there's an alias that children use, you know, like...
I don't know what it's called... but it's something like "butchaga-butchaga.
Like a piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy piggy
I don't know.
I don't know, it was a ridiculous name or something like that.
I see. So perhaps we are called that because we are in Hyogo Prefecture.
I don't think there are people like that in the Kanto region.
Which Hyogo people? Hyogo people are Kaiser. Kaiser? Kaiser.
Kaiser is a German word meaning "emperor," isn't it?
What's the name of the bug I'm trying to say right now?
Hmm? What is it?
Think about it.
What I want to say is...
I don't know.
Amistad.
Amistad?
I didn't say that. Are you okay? Hey, guys. Hey, hey, hey. That's a weird name list. We're not having this conversation anymore.
I want what you want. She's asking me what's the name behind the one I want to say. I said, "I don't know. I said, "Amistad.
What? Oh, you got a ringing in your ears. Tinnitus? I've got it, too. I've got it, too. It's a ringing. It's always ringing. It's the same.
It's like, you know, it's like... it's like... it's like... it's like... it's in my ear.
It's funny, because we're not even on the same page, and I'm not listening to you.
Kaiser.
Gaither.
I don't know what a cow's tail is.
Cows have tails.
There are a lot of things... and some bugs don't even have tails.
What's this?
Wow!
I'm halfway through writing all the titles!
What do you mean?
I can't write any more.
You mean you can't write any more?
That's amazing.
Like a famous painter.
I can't write any more.
Like the paintings he was doing right before he died.
That's great.
Well, then, doctor, please.
Gaither, this way, please.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you any more.
What?
Shells.
Shell.
Like a shellfish.
Ahhh...
Kaisa?
Okinawan style.
Or is that...
What is this?
A little muddy.
Gaither.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
What? What? What's wrong?
Are you okay? This is from Evangelion.
Dendendendendendendendendendendendend.
You guys get the picture.
The apostles are coming.
Oh, shit.
The apostles are coming!
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Great disaster... great disaster... great disaster... great disaster... it's an apostle, isn't it?
Please...
I'm Gaither.
Wow, here he comes!
Oh my God!
I haven't seen you in a while.
I bet his eyes are on top of his head.
Where do bugs put their eyes?
I mean, where are their eyes? I mean, they do have eyes, though.
I'm a goldbug.
That's why I'm glowing.
Golden bug, because it's shiny.
Because it looks strong. That guy is definitely strong.
Gaither.
But there's a little bit of Guy
He's got a little bit of a gai?
But isn't there a special kind of bug?
I mean, there's some kind of a crayfish beetle that has a guy, right? I don't think so. I don't think they have a mussel.
No, I don't think that's what you're thinking of.
Something shiny like that, like a giger, shiny, shiny, shiny.
Well, well, well, by the way, it's pretty close. Oh, my God!
Oh, wow! "Giger" is a word from the Hyogo dialect.
It's a Hyogo dialect word for a stink bug!
Nice try! This, this, this!
Oh, it's behind the foot... Yes, it's a bit close, you could say.
No, it's true, but, wow!
Gai Girl, Gai Za, Gai Za, Gai Za, Komal, Hyogo Prefecture...
He says, "It's not Okinawa." Well, say "Gaither.
By the way, this person also says that in my area, Ako city, Hyogo prefecture, they call this seagull "Geyser.
In my area, in Ako city, Hyogo prefecture, they call this bug "Gaither" or "Gaither" or "Gaita" or "Gaita".
It's called "gaiter" or "gaiter" or "gaiter. It is a common practice in my hometown, but people in the Kanto region do not understand it at all.
It is so common in my hometown, but it was not understood at all by people in Kanto area. I knew this guy was a gaita gaita gaita. Guida guida guida guida guida guida guida guida. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. I guess that's how it is. Can I ask you to be quiet for a minute?
Can I ask you to be quiet for a minute with the head of the gaya geiko? Properly, properly, properly. It's crazy, isn't it? I didn't do it, I didn't do it. It's like, "I didn't do it.
I didn't do it, I didn't do it.
Yes, yes, yes, by the way, is it the one that the sister just mentioned?
Buttako possession? Ah, buttako! Buttako possession!
Yes, yes, yes.
In Iwate, female pigs are called "butakko".
So the kids were the first to say it, and then it spread to the local kids and was passed down.
I think that's how it was originally.
I see.
Well, well, well, well, well, well...
I'm sorry, do you have an exorcism recommendation for me?
Recommended exotics?
I don't know, it's not coming.
Oh, come on.
By the way, for those of you who are watching this...
I have a favor to ask you.
A notice?
I'd like to make a new product for the Devil on Board.
I'd like to make a new line of goods.
If it's possible, I'd love to hear from you all about what you'd like to see in it.
What a surprise.
What's wrong, Princess Rice?
What's wrong, Princess?
Well, I haven't announced my birthday present yet.
I couldn't make it, so I want a beer mug.
I want one.
Sure you do.
Like this one. I want one like this so bad.
It's a beer mug. It's nice. It would be cute if it had a red Reville logo on it.
Some people know I couldn't make it here. I couldn't make it.
I think we should make servers and stuff like that.
I want one. I just said I want it.
Great!
If you have any, please send them to us.
I'd love to have one of those. In the corner.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I don't know... corners.
What do you want? This...
X
Yes, I'm on it.
Brackets 9, Twitter, the brackets and the fonts...
And what's that again? A website? The show?
You can buy stuff from anywhere.
Yeah.
Like, I'd like you to make something like this.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I hope you'll keep sending them to us.
I think so, yes.
Yes, I think so.
And from me...
May I make an announcement? What?
You drew this picture?
You're going to announce it? Yes. Does it matter?
No, it doesn't. I have an announcement.
Yeah, it's not. I'm just letting you know.
Nakashima drew Gaither.
This Sunday, this Sunday...
Oh, my God. Kalimen Ryer.
Shall we switch to that?
Ready, publish!
We're going to perform at the Upcycle Fest 2024 Local Heroes Show!
Isn't that great?
And it's going to be at the Kawasaki Convention on Sunday, August 18th from around 1pm.
Local Hero Gathering" means that local heroes from all over the world will gather together.
Yes, there will be 25 local heroes.
One of them is...
Wow, that's great!
Yes, it's suddenly this Sunday, the 18th.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
I wonder if they're going to fight for the Hero Award there.
What? But they've never fought in the movie.
Yes! Yes! I wonder if I can do it.
I'm a little nervous because I can do it, but you know, they might be filming the full-length version of Kamen Liar somewhere.
I see.
I'm sure you'll be able to do it.
That's great.
No, it's pretty soon, isn't it? No, it's very soon. This Sunday.
This Sunday.
What's up with the sudden decision?
Wow, that's great! They said he's the only one.
They said he's the only one.
If you have time, please come and see us at the Kawasaki Convention Hall.
They're going to know. They're going to know.
Did you draw this?
Yes. Yes, the Kokeshi Bird of Kariwenleier.
I don't know what it is, but it looks something like this.
It has four arms!
Wow, you painstakingly drew this yourself!
It's not bad at all!
We had a big one-hour break, and I worked very hard during that time, but this is the best I could do.
And remember, if you're going to write down memories like this, you should be careful about this.
I'm not used to that part.
And that's just the first letter.
And I made a mistake once.
This is the second one.
I see.
By all means, everyone!
The Great Gathering Award!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Please come to Albee's.
August 18th.
So it's Sunday.
Sunday.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it's Sunday.
Okay, everyone.
So we'll be able to see the Kalimin Liar in person?
Yes, that's right.
Yo! Yes!
And there are many local heroes.
Yes!
You can see them.
Look!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well...
Well, let's see... like this.
We're about to start the live broadcast.
And thank you for the level charge.
Thank you very much.
We've received so many of them.
It's Famien, isn't it?
We are going to be at the Famien this weekend.
But there's a typhoon coming.
Yamanaka?
Yes, sir.
The 17th?
The 17th and 18th.
The 17th is a little early.
The 16th is the worst.
16 and 17 are a little bit...
I'm sure 18 is fine.
Maybe 17 will be okay, too.
Don't let the typhoon get you down.
That's right.
It'll blow away... Oh, don't worry, the masked liar will blow away the typhoon.
Kuru-kuru-kuru...
Well, well, well, well, well...
Well, let's see next week at 8:00 p.m.
Well, thank you very much again this week.
That's a bargain.
Thank you very much.
Master, it's okay.
Just do it.
It won't cost you anything.
It's not like they charge you 8 yen a time.
Be realistic.
Just do it.
Just do it!